Guide to the New American Library Archive 1943-1962 MSS.070
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: New American Library, Editorial/Author Files
  - Huie, William Bradford, "The Hero of Iwo Jima and Other Stories,", 1960-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2382)
  - Huie, William Bradford, "Hotel Mamie Stover,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2383)
  - Huie, William Bradford, "The Patriot,", 1961 (Box 79, Folder 2384)
  - Hutter, Catherine, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2385)
  - Hyde, H. Montgomery, "History of Pornography,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2386)
  - Ibert, J.C., and J. Charles, "Love the French Way (L'Amour et Les Francais),", 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2387)
  - Ilton, Paul, "The Sons of Darkness,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2388)
  - Irving, Clifford, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2389)
  - Irving, Washington, "The Sketch Book,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2390)
  - James, Henry, "The Madonna of the Future and Other Early Stories,", 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2391)
  - James, Henry, "The Marriage and Other Stories,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2392)
  - Janson, H.W., "History of Art,", 1957-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2393)
  - Jarman, T.L., "The Rise and Fall of Nazi Germany,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2394)
  - Jerusalem Bible, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2395)
  - Jesus, Carolina Maria de, "Cuarto de Despejo,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2396)
  - Johnson, Vernon, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2397)
  - Johnston, Albert, "In the Corridor,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2398)
  - Jones, Howard Mumford, "Goal For Americans" (no date), undated (Box 80, Folder 2399)
  - Joyce, James, "Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2400)
  - Kane, Henry, "Run for Doom,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2401)
  - Kantor, Mackinley, "Spirit Lake,", 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2402)
  - Kato, Kyoko, and Hilary Cox, "Japanese Folk Tales,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2403)
  - Kauffeld, Carl, "How to Know the American Reptiles,", 1953-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2404)
  - Kaufman, Barry, "The Right People,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2405)
  - Keller, Gottfried, "Martin Salander,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2406)
  - Kelley, William, "A Fugue for Seven Strumpets," "A Still Small Voice,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2407)
  - Kennedy, Jay Richard, "Short Term,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2408)
  - Kennedy, Malcolm D., "A History of Japan,", 1960-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2409)
  - Kenneth, Claire, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2410)
  - Kenneth, Claire, "The Love Riddle,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2411)
  - Kentfield, Calvin, "The Small Rain,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2412)
  - King, Alexander, "I Should Have Kissed Her More,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2413)
  - King, Henry, "Challenge of the Cosmos,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2414)
  - King, Henry, "Exploration of the Universe,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2415)
  - Kipling, Rudyard, "The Jungle Books,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2416)
  - Kirkwood, James, "There Must Be a Pony,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2417)
  - Kirsch, Robert, "Fair Trial,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2418)
  - Kline, Herbert, Simon Bolivar project, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2419)
  - Knight, Arthur, "The Liveliest Art,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2420)
  - Koestler, Arthur, "Darkness at Noon,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2421)
  - Koff, Richard M., "How Does it Work,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2422)
  - Komroff, Manuel, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2423)
  - Korngold, Ralph, "Citizen Toussaint,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2424)
  - Kriegel, Leonard, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2425)
  - Kuhn, Thomas, and Charles Gillispie, "History of Scientific Thought,", 1958-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2426)
  - Laclos, Chodorlos de, "Les Liaisons Dangereuses,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2427)
  - Lacy, Ed, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2428)
  - Lafayette, Madame de, "The Princess of Cleves,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2429)
  - Lampedusa, Giuseppe de, "The Leopard,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2430)
  - Langdon-Davies, John, "On the Nature of Man,", 1958-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2431)
  - Langer, Suzanne, "Feeling and Form,", 1951-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2432)
  - Lanternari, Vittorio, "Movimenti Religiosi,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2433)
  - Lawrence, D.H., "Lady Chatterley's Lover,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2434)
  - Lawrence, John, "A History of Russia,", 1959-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2435)
  - Legman, G., "Love and Death,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2436)
  - Lemisch, L. Jesse, "The Autobiography of Benjamin Franklin and Selected Papers,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2437)
  - Leskov, Nikolai, "Selected Stories,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2438)
  - Lewis, Alfred Allan, "A Striving After Wind,", 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2439)
  - Lewis, Oscar, "The Children of Sanchez,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2440)
  - Lewis, Roy, and Rosemary Stewart, "The Managers,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2441)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2442)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, "Babbitt,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2443)
  - Lewis, Sinclair, "Main Street,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2444)
  - Ley, Willie, "Missiles, Moon-Probes, and Megaparsecs,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2445)
  - Lindsey, Cynthia, "The Natives are Restless,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2446)
  - Lobsenz, Herbert, "Vangel Griffin,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2447)
  - Loeff, Ted, general correspondence, 1962 (Box 80, Folder 2448)
  - Lorca, Garcia, "The Tragicomedy of Christobita and Dona Rosita,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2449)
  - Lord, Russell, "The Care of the Land,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2450)
  - Love, Edmond G., "Arsenic and Red Tape,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2451)
  - Lovell, C.B., "The Individual and the Universe,", 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2452)
  - Lowry, Malcolm, "Ultramarine,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2453)
  - Lubac, Henri de, "Catholicism,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2454)
  - Lucretius, "The Nature of Things,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2455)
  - Lynds, Dennis, "Combat Soldier,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2456)
  - Lynds, Dennis, "The Man in the Turned Down Hat,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2457)
  - Lyons, Augusta Wallace, "Season of Desire,", 1960-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2458)
  - McAfee, Thomas, "Poems and Stories,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2459)
  - MacAndrew, Andrew, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2460)
  - McCabe, Charles, "Fearless Spectator,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2461)
  - MacDonagh, Donagh, "The Informer,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2462)
  - McGuinness, Eugene V., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2463)
  - Madrigal, Margarita, and Giuseppina Salvadori, "See It and Say It in Italian,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2464)
  - Madrigal, Margarita, "See It and Say It in Spanish,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2465)
  - Magarshack, David, "Selected Tales,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2466)
  - Mailer, Norman, "The Naked and the Dead,", 1950-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2467)
  - Malamud, Bernard, "A New Life,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2468)
  - Mann, Abby, "A Child is Waiting,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2469)
  - Mann, Abby, "Judgment at Nuremberg,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2470)
  - Manning, Robert, project, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2471)
  - Mantley, John, "Garibaldi's Rebs,", 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2472)
  - Mao, Tse-Tung, "Basic Writings,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2473)
  - Maritain, Jacques, "Preface to Metaphysics,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2474)
  - Marks, Lawrence, "Women and Children Last,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2475)
  - Martin, Don, "Mad's Maddest Artist,", 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2476)
  - Martin, Kay [pseud. Converse, Jane], "Second Chance Nurse,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2477)
  - Mason, Richard, "The Fever Tree,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2478)
  - Mathewson, R.D., "The United Nations and How It Works,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2479)
  - Matthew, Helen, "Asia in the Modern World,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2480)
  - Maurer, David W., "The Big Con,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2481)
  - Maxwell, Gilbert, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2482)
  - Mead, Margaret, "New Lives for Old,", 1960 (Box 80, Folder 2483)
  - Medawar, P.B., "The Future of Man,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2484)
  - Mehling, Harold, "The Time-Killer,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2485)
  - Meldon, Maurice, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2486)
  - Melville, Herman, "Billy Budd and Other Tales,", 1946-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2487)
  - Merimee, Prosper, "Carmen and Columba,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2488)
  - Merton, Thomas, "The New Man and Disputed Questions,", 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2489)
  - Merwin, W.S., "The Cid,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2490)
  - Metraux, Guy S., "Journal of World History,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2491)
  - MGM project, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2492)
  - Miller, Henry, "Tropic of Cancer,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2493)
  - Miller, Max, "Holladay Street,", 1961-1962 (Box 80, Folder 2494)
  - Miller, Ron, "The Comic,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2495)
  - Miller, Wade, "Calamity Fair,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2496)
  - Miller, Wade, "Deadly Weapon,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2497)
  - Miller, Wade, "Killer's Choice,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2498)
  - Miller, Wade, "Murder Charge,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2499)
  - Milton, John, "Paradise Lost,", 1951-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2500)
  - Mintz, Jerome, "The Diary of Samuel Pepys,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2501)
  - Modisett, Mitchell, "Clayton's Debt of Honor,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2502)
  - Monahan, James, "Before I Sleep,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2503)
  - Montagu, Ashley, "Man - His First Million Years,", 1957-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2504)
  - Moore, Geoffrey, "American Prose Today,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2505)
  - Moore, Harry T., "Twentieth Century Literature,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2506)
  - Moravia, Alberto, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2507)
  - Moravia, Alberto, "The Empty Canvas,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2508)
  - Moravia, Alberto, "Mistaken Ambitions,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2509)
  - Moravia, Alberto, "Two Adolescents,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2510)
  - More, Thomas, "The Essential Writings of Thomas More,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2511)
  - Morehead, Albert H., "Bi-Lingual Dictionaries,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2512)
  - Morehead, Albert H., "Crossword Puzzle Book #1,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2513)
  - Morehead, Albert H., "Crossword Puzzle Book #2,", 1959-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2514)
  - Morehead, Albert H., "Crossword Puzzle Book #3,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2515)
  - Morehead, Albert H., "Thesaurus,", 1960-1961 (Box 80, Folder 2516)
  - Morehead, Albert H., "Third - Fifth Grade Dictionary,", 1961 (Box 80, Folder 2517)
  - Morhaim, Victoria, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2518)
  - Morhaim, Victoria, "The Girl Who Had Everything,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2519)
  - Morris, Paul C., "Science and a Humanized World,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2520)
  - Motter, T.H. Vail, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2521)
  - Motz, Lloyd, "This is Outer Space,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2522)
  - Muller, Herbert J., "The Loom of History,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2523)
  - Murray, Margaret, "The Genesis of Religion,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2524)
  - Nelson and Goldwin, "Toward the Liberally Educated Executive,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2525)
  - Neustadt, Richard E., "Presidential Power,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2526)
  - Newman, John Henry, "The Essential Writings of John Henry Cardinal Newman,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2527)
  - Newland, Constance A.., "Myself and I,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2528)
  - Norse, Harold, "Almonds Like Pink Snow,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2529)
  - Nutting, Anthony, "Lawrence of Arabia,", 1960-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2530)
  - O'Connor, Flannery, "The Violent Bear It Away,", 1960 (Box 81, Folder 2531)
  - O'Dea, Thomas F., "American Catholic Dilemma,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2532)
  - O'Flaherty, Liam, "The Informer,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2533)
  - Olay, Lionel, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2534)
  - O'Neal, Charles, and Victor Trivas, "The Cheka Story,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2535)
  - O'Neil, Russell, "Climate of Violence,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2536)
  - O'Neill, Eugene, "Long Day's Journey Into Night,", 1956-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2537)
  - Onis, Harriet de, "The Golden Serpent,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2538)
  - Opik, Ernest J., "The Oscillating Universe,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2539)
  - Orkow, Ben, "Deep Freeze,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2540)
  - Orwell, George, "1984,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2541)
  - Overholser, Wayne D., "The Crossing,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2542)
  - Ovid, "The Love Poems of Ovid,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2543)
  - Packer, Peter, "The Love Thieves,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2544)
  - Packer, Peter, "No My Darling Daughter,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2545)
  - Packer, Peter, captain story, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2546)
  - Panduro, Leif, "Kick Me in the Traditions,", 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2547)
  - Pares, Bernard, "A History of Russia,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2548)
  - Parkinson, C. Northcote, "East and West,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2549)
  - Parkinson, C. Northcote, "Revolting Colonies,", 1960 (Box 81, Folder 2550)
  - Pascal, Blaise, "Pensees,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2551)
  - Pearl, Richard, "Successful Mineral Collecting and Prospecting,", 1957-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2552)
  - Peterson, Roger Tory, "How to Know the Birds,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2553)
  - Philosophy Series, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2554)
  - Phipps, Helen, "The San Rafael Story,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2555)
  - Pickthall, M.M., "The Meaning of the Glorious Koran,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2556)
  - Pinney, Roy, "How to Know the Reptiles and Amphibians,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2557)
  - Plamenatz, John, "Man and Society,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2558)
  - Playboy Anthology, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2559)
  - Plenn, J.H., "Texas Hellion,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2560)
  - Plutarch, "Moralia,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2561)
  - Poe, Edgar Allen, "Fall of the House of Usher,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2562)
  - Ponce de Leon, Florence, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2563)
  - Post, Charles Johnson, "The Little War of Private Post,", 1959-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2564)
  - Potter, John Dean, "General Yashamita,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2565)
  - Pratt, Rex T., "You Tell My Son,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2566)
  - Preece, Harold, Dalton epic, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2567)
  - Prescott, William H., "The Conquest of Peru,", 1959-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2568)
  - Prevost, Abbe, "Manon Lescaut,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2569)
  - Prince, Martin V.H., "Books That Changed the World,", 1958-1960 (Box 81, Folder 2570)
  - Pushkin, Alexander S., "The Queen of Spades,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2571)
  - Quigley, Carroll, "The Evolution of Civilizations,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2572)
  - Ramati, Alexander, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2573)
  - Ramati, Alexander, "Rebel Against the Light,", 1959-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2574)
  - Rand, Lester, "Teenagers Say,", 1962 (Box 81, Folder 2575)
  - Randall, Clarence B., "The Folklore of Management,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2576)
  - Rapport, Samuel, and Helen Wright, "The Crust of the Earth,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2577)
  - Ratcliff, J.C., "The Human Machine,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2578)
  - Rawson, Tabor, "I Want to Live,", 1959-1960 (Box 81, Folder 2579)
  - Rawson, Tabor, "Kowloon,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2580)
  - Rayner, William, "Gourmet Cooking by the Clock,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2581)
  - Reed, Henry Hope Jr., general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2582)
  - Rice, Cy, "Errol and Me,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2583)
  - Richardson, John, "Ghosts,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2584)
  - Robbins, Harold, "The Carpetbaggers,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2585)
  - Roberts, Elizabeth Madox, "The Great Meadow,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2586)
  - Roberts, William H., Hispanic translations, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2587)
  - Robertson, Frank, "Rawhide,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2588)
  - Robertson, Frank, "Wanted: Dead or Alive,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2589)
  - Robinson, Bradley, "The Mill,", 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2590)
  - Robinson, David, "The Confession of Alma Quartier,", 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2591)
  - Robinson, Marie N., "The Power of Sexual Surrender,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2592)
  - Roche, Paul, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2593)
  - Roche, Paul, "Oedipus; Plays of Sophocles,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2594)
  - Roche, Paul, "Orestes; Plays of Aeschylus,", 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2595)
  - Roche, Paul, "Plautus,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2596)
  - Roche, Paul, "Prometheus Bound,", 1960-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2597)
  - Roche, Paul, "Vessel of Dishonor,", 1958-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2598)
  - Rochemont, Louis D., "The Roman Spring of Mrs. Stone,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2599)
  - Romains, Jules, "Death of a Nobody,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2600)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, "The Rough Riders,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2601)
  - Rosenthal, Milton, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2602)
  - Roshwald, Mordechai, "Level 7,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2603)
  - Roskolenko, Harry, "Congaii,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2604)
  - Roskolenko, Harry, "Exotique,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2605)
  - Rossiter, Clinton, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2606)
  - Rothenberg, Robert E., "Health and Medical Care After 60,", 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2607)
  - Rothenberg, Robert E., "Medical Dictionary and Health Manual,", 1960-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2608)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Great Dialogues of Plato,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2609)
  - Rouse, W.H.D., "Odyssey,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2610)
  - Rowe, Colin, general correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 81, Folder 2611)
  - Ruark, Robert, "Uhuru,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2612)
  - Rugoff, Milton, "The Mutiny on Board the H.M.S. Bounty,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2613)
  - Rugoff, Milton, "The Travels of Marco Polo,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2614)
  - Ruitenbeck, Hendrick M., "The Individual and the Crowd,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2615)
  - Russell, Bertrand, "Human Society in Ethics and Politics,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2616)
  - Russell, Bertrand, India book, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2617)
  - St. Johns, George, "The Democratic Way of Life,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2618)
  - Saltykov-Shchedrin, Mikhail, "The Golovlovs,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2619)
  - Santillana, Giorgio de, "The Origins of Scientific Thought, Vol. I,", 1958-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2620)
  - Santillana, Giorgio de, "The Emergence of Scientific Thought, Vol. II,", 1958-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2621)
  - Santillana, Giorgio de, "The Shaping of Scientific Thought, Vols. III and IV,", 1958-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2622)
  - Santillana, Giorgio de, "The Challenge of Scientific Thought, Vol. V,", 1959-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2623)
  - Sargent, E.N., "African Boy,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2624)
  - Scandinavian Classics, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2625)
  - Schaefer, Jack, "Company of Cowards,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2626)
  - Schilling, Wilfrid, "The Fear Makers,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2627)
  - Schneider, Daniel S., "The Psychoanalyst and the Artist,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2628)
  - Schoenfeld, Dudley D., "The Crime and the Criminal,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2629)
  - Schonfield, Hugh, "Reader's Companion to Biblical Literature,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2630)
  - Schorer, Mark, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2631)
  - Science series, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2632)
  - Scott, Paul, "The Love Pavilion,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2633)
  - Sell, Henry, "Buffalo Bill,", 1961-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2634)
  - Sendrey, Alfred, and Mildred Norton, "The Music of Ancient Israel,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2635)
  - Serguine, Jacques, "Special People,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2636)
  - Shakespeare series, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2637)
  - Sheckley, Robert, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2638)
  - Shipley, Clarke, "The Executions,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2639)
  - Shipley, Clarke, "The Man Downstairs,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2640)
  - Shirer, William L., "Midcentury Journey,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2641)
  - Shirreffs, Gordon D., "The Last Man Alive,", 1960-1962 (Box 81, Folder 2642)
  - Shirreffs, Gordon D., "The Valiant Bugles,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2643)
  - Sholokhov, Mikhail, "Harvest on the Don,", 1960-1961 (Box 81, Folder 2644)
  - Shulman, Irving, "The Roots of Fury,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2645)
  - Shute, Neville, "Trustee From the Toolroom,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2646)
  - Sichel, Pierre, "Man With a Certain Talent,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2647)
  - Signet Classics, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2648)
  - Sillitoe, Alan, "The General,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2649)
  - Silone, Ignazio, "Bread and Wine,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2650)
  - Simcoe, Ben, "The Evil That Men Do,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2651)
  - Simcoe, Ben, "A War, Not So Cold,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2652)
  - Sinclair, Upton, "The Jungle,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2653)
  - Sinclair, Upton, "My Lifetime in Letters,", 1961 (Box 81, Folder 2654)
  - Slonin, Marc, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2655)
  - Small, Peter, "Sea Frontier,", 1959-1961 (Box 82, Folder 2656)
  - Smith, Fred, "633 Squadron,", 1959 (Box 82, Folder 2657)
  - Smith, Lillian, "Killers of the Dream,", 1954-1956 (Box 82, Folder 2658)
  - Smith, Lillian, "One Hour,", 1956-1960 (Box 82, Folder 2659)
  - Smith, T.V., and Edward Lindeman, "The Democratic Way of Life,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2660)
  - Smith, Wilfred Cantwell, "Islam in Modern History,", 1957-1961 (Box 82, Folder 2661)
  - Sneider, Vern, "A Long Way From Home,", 1960 (Box 82, Folder 2662)
  - Spade, Jack, "Bridge Burn,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2663)
  - Spicer, Bart, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2664)
  - Spillane, Mickey, "The Deep,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2665)
  - Sprinchorn, Evert, "Genius of the Scandinavian Theater,", 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 2666)
  - Springer, John, "Innocent in Alaska,", 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 2667)
  - Standing, E.M., "Maria Montessori: Her Life and Work,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2668)
  - Starkie, Walter, Spanish volume for Signet Classic, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2669)
  - Stein, Gertrude, Mentor book, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2670)
  - Stephens, James, "Crock of Gold,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2671)
  - Stephens, James, "Deirdre,", 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 2672)
  - Stewart, Rosemary, general correspondence, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2673)
  - Stone, Irving, "The Agony and the Ecstasy,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2674)
  - Storm, Theodore, "The Rider on the White Horse and Other Stories,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2675)
  - Stuart, Zefa, "Capa,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2676)
  - Stefferud, Alfred, "The Wonderful World of Books,", 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 2677)
  - Styron, William, "The Confessions of Nat Turner,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2678)
  - Styron, William, "Set This House on Fire,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2679)
  - Suggs, Robert C., "An Expedition to the Marquesas Islands,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2680)
  - Swarthout, Glendon, "Welcome to Thebes,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2681)
  - Szilard, Leo, "Memoirs,", 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 2682)
  - Tacitus, "The Agricola, Germania, and Histories,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2683)
  - Tanizaki, Junichiro, "The Key,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2684)
  - Tarkington, Booth, "Alice Adams,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2685)
  - Telfer, Dariel, "The Guilty Ones,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2686)
  - Thackeray, William M., "Vanity Fair,", 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 2687)
  - Theobald, Robert, "The Challenge of Abundance,", 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 2688)
  - Thompson, Jim, "Compulsion to Confess,", 1959-1960 (Box 82, Folder 2689)
  - Thompson, Jim, "The Transgressors,", 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 2690)
  - Thompson, Lovell, Philosophers series, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2691)
  - Thoreau, Henry D., "A Week on the Concord and Merrimack,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2692)
  - Thoreau, Henry D., "Walden,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2693)
  - Thorp and Bunker, "Crow Killer,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2694)
  - Thorp, Willard, general correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 82, Folder 2695)
  - Thurber, James, "The Years With Ross,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2696)
  - Toland, John, "Battle: The Story of the Bulge,", 1959 (Box 82, Folder 2697)
  - Toland, John, "But Not in Shame,", 1961 (Box 82, Folder 2698)
  - Tolstoy, Alexey, "Peter the First,", 1960 (Box 82, Folder 2699)